翻譯: sumsmit Amber 阿朽
猜猜誰馬上就要去
Guess who's going on a get-away to the most
- 世界上最浪漫的地方了  - 去斐濟嗎
- romantic place ever? - Fiji?
校對: 阿朽
美夢終于成真了
We're finally doing it?
我要去和海龜一起游泳了
I'm gonna get to swim with a sea turtle!
后期: UU123
你知道什么和去斐濟游泳一樣棒嗎
You know what's kinda like swimming in Fiji?
去新澤西打高爾夫
Golfing in New Jersey.
我們可以在YouTube上看海龜視頻
But we can look at sea turtles on YouTube.
壓制: B B
我每個周末都看
I do that every weekend.
那不一樣的
That's not the same.
拜托了 親愛的 這可是CNBC的慈善高爾夫球賽
Come on, honey. CNBC charity golf event.
唉 對我來說都很無聊
Ugh, those things are so boring for me.
你被拉去各種合照
You always end up getting pulled into a million photo-ups
我就要整個周末都對他們微笑 鼓掌
and I spend the weekend politely golf clapping.
我鼓掌很用力的 你娶我的時候就知道了
I clap big, Mike. You knew that when you married me.
我只是不喜歡他們的殷勤
I just don't like all the attention.
- 哦 真的嗎 Mike  - 好吧 也許我很享受 但是
- Oh, yeah, really, Mike? - Well, maybe I do, but,
這不是重點
this isn't about that.
這次活動舉辦地是沿岸莊園
The event's being held at the Shore Side Manor.
噢 有點意思
Uh, game changer.
沿岸莊園是二十年前Mike向我求婚的地方
Shore Side Manor is where Mike proposed to me 20 years ago.
那時候我們沒幾個錢
We were pretty broke back then,
只能住在最差的房間里
so we had to stay in the worst room in the hotel.
號稱有花園景觀 但是我們唯一觀到的
They call it garden view, but the only thing we viewed
就是一群打高爾夫的人在隨地小便
was a bunch of golfers peeing.
我們正好在前九個球洞和后九個球洞之間
We were right between the front nine and the back nine.
我還真看到一個人的乳溝了(諧音前九洞)
I actually saw a guy's front line.
這次我們去住那的海景套房
This time we're going to an ocean view suite.
我去打幾桿球
And I'll hit a few golf balls,
然后就是我們的浪漫時間了
and the rest of the time will be nothing but romance.
- 說好了哦  - 我要做你愛的海龜
- You promise. - I'll be your seaturtle of love,
把浪漫之蛋埋到沙子里
and we will bury our eggs of romance in the sand,
不說了 抱一下
Forget it, come here.
噢 你們注意一點好嗎
Oh! You people are machines.
這個家里就沒有一個房間
Can't there be one room in this house
是沒有人在接吻的嗎
where people are not kissing?
有啊 你的房間
Yeah, that'd be your room, Ian.
哦 Mike 別這樣
Oh, Mike. Come on.
我們在Ian的房間里親熱過很多次的
You know we've made out plenty of times in Ian's room.
又 見 彩 虹
第一季  第七集
電波誠譯
- 媽媽 我們的麥片吃完了  - 噓
- Mom, we're out of cereal! - Shh.
媽媽正在度假呢
Mom's on vacation.
躺在一張舒服的吊床上
Right now I'm easing into a hammock,
放松
I'm relaxed--
你們怎么都不用杯托
are none of you using your coaster?
我們得先把你送走
Oh, boy, we gotta get you out of here.
Felix不來約會了
Well, Felix canceled on me.
我很確定 我們完了
I'm pretty sure it's over.
不會吧 你那么喜歡他
Oh, no. You liked him.
他從來沒想盜用你的身份
He never tried to steal your identity.
身份盜用是通過在線網站等方式進行約會的常見騙局
他真的是如意郎君
He was a real catch.
我已經做好心理準備了
I had this whole spread prepared.
我猜這又是一個和往常一樣的周六夜晚了
Guess it's just another Saturday night
老姑姑Leigh百無聊賴的打發時間
with nothing to do for Old Aunt Leigh.
還得照看Graham 你不會忘了吧
Except babysit Graham, or have you forgotten?
Michael 你說什么呢
Michael, what are you implying?
我怎么可能忘掉我的寶貝侄子
I could never forget my baby nephew.
我完全忘記了
I totally forgot.
希望你餓了 寶貝
Hope you're hungry, buddy.
我做了一頓大餐
I made a big dinner that was in no way
絕對不是受到<愛你九周半>的影響
inspired by 9 1/2 Weeks.
再見 爸爸
Bye, dad.
好了 我和媽媽要出發了
Okay, kiddos. We gotta boogie.
這里是你們的天下了
The place is yours.
我們走了 不要玩得太瘋哦
Don't have too much fun without us.
- 愛你 再見  - 放心吧
- Love you. Bye. - We won't.
會想你們的
We'll miss you.
這些笨蛋 真是好騙
Those trusting fools.
周末我們把房子租給別人了
We rented out the apartment for the weekend
因為我們是天才
'cause we're geniuses.
你可以在網上賺到一大筆錢
You can make a killing online
出租曼哈頓一套四臥兩浴的公寓
for a four-bedroom, two-bath in Manhattan.
- 狗關起來  - 搞定
- Dog in the kennel? - Check.
- 換床單  - 搞定
- Sheets changed? - Check.
枕邊薄荷糖
Mints on the pillow?
這樣有度假酒店的感覺嘛
For that resort feel.
噢 也許會留些小費呢
Ooh, maybe they'll leave a tip.
再回到這里真是太棒了
It feels so good to be back here.
哦 要死 我把比基尼落在車上了
Oh, damn, I left my bikini in the car.
Annie 外面才13度
Annie, it's 56 degrees outside.
我就在泳池邊躺躺
Hey, I am laying by that pool.
- 這也不行嗎  - Henry先生
- You let me have this. - Mr. Henry...
可以和你照張相嗎
Mind if we take a picture?
- 你是我們的人生楷模  - 哦 謝謝
- You're a real inspiration to us. - Oh, thanks, guys.
- 不過我和我妻子在一塊呢  - 不 沒關系
- But I'm kind of with my wife. - No, no, no, no, it's fine.
你和大家聊聊
You greet your public,
我回去拿我的泳衣
and I will go and get my swimsuit.
好吧 把我舉起來 我躺在你們胳膊上
Okay, well, lift me up. I'll lie across your arms.
再用我的相機來一張
Get one on my camera too.
祝您愉快
Enjoy your stay.
- 嗨 你好  - 歡迎
- Hey, how are you? - Welcome.
- 謝謝
- Thanks.
呃 我正排著隊呢
Uh, I was in line.
不好意思 沒看見你
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't see you there.
好吧 我雖然不高 但也沒有矮到你看不見的地步吧
Well, I know I'm short, but I'm not that short.
哦 不 我沒看見你是因為 我是盲人
Uh, no, I didn't see you because I'm blind.
登記入住 這是我的身份證
Just checking in. Here's my ID.
我很抱歉沒注意到你是盲人 但是
Well, I'm sorry I didn't notice you were blind, but--
但是 但是 但是 但是什么
But-- but-- but-- but-- but-- but what?
但是你還是排到我前面去了
But you're still in front of me in line.
你以為我瞎得不知道我在你前面嗎
Oh, because I'm blind I don't know where I am in line?
不 你當然知道 只是
No, you totally do. It's just that--
好了好了 別說了
You know what, hold that thought.
- 快點搞定吧  - 好了
- Just let me finish.  - Here you are.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
現在 無論如何
Now, by all means.
Vernon
Vernon.
算了 無所謂
Well, as long as you're done.
嗨 登記入住 我是Mike Henry
Hi, checking in. Mike Henry.
好的 你將入住我們的園景套房
Great, we've got you in a garden view suite.
不不不
Oh, no, no.
我們想要的是海景套房
We were expecting an ocean view suite.
這樣啊
Oh.
剛才那位先生要了最后一間了
That gentleman just got the last one.
真的嗎
Really?
看上去是有點浪費了啊
Kind of seems like a waste of an ocean view suite.
因為
Because...
我懂的
I got it.
你的鑰匙
Here's your key.
今晚是我的第三次約會 可是在最后一分鐘
I had a third date tonight, but the guy canceled
那個家伙不來了
at the last minute.
前景堪憂啊
Not a good sign.
為什么
Why?
第三次約會是這樣的
Third date's make or break--
你帶他回家 喂點吃的
You take him home, feed him some figs,
然后他凝視著你的眼睛
then he looks into your eyes and says
說出你期待很久的那三個字
those three words you've been longing to hear--
"我離了"
"I'm getting divorced."
我朋友Tommy的爸爸媽媽也離婚了
My friend Tommy's parents are divorced.
所以呢
Good story.
看來老姑姑Leigh
Yep, I guess Old Aunt Leigh's
注定和約會無緣了
just destined to be dateless.
我來和你約會
I'll be your date.
噢
Oh.
真是紳士
Such a gentleman.
為什么你頭頂
Why is your hair a different color
頭發的顏色不一樣
on the top of your head?
紳士是不問問題的 Graham
Gentlemen don't ask questions, Graham.
Annie 你不冷嗎
- - Annie, you must be freezing.
精神大于肉體 我要保持鮮活的度假之心
Mind over matter-- Needed to keep the vacation spirit alive
因為我們沒能訂到海景套房
since we didn't get the ocean view suite.
好消息是
Oh, good news.
我預約了情侶按摩
I booked us a couples massage.
我們就不去晚宴了吧
So I figured we could skip the banquet,
去吃一頓安靜浪漫的二人晚餐
have a quiet, romantic dinner for two.
是在室內 對吧
Oh, that's inside, right?
我的腳趾已經沒有知覺了
Because I can't really feel my toes.
- 嗨 Mike  - 嗨 Harris
- Hey, Mike.  - Hey, Harris.
重返球場了啊 嘿 Annie
Back in the game. Hey, Annie.
- 套件羊毛衫  - 我知道
- Throw on a fleece. - I know.
準備好去給圣阿比蓋爾醫院
So ready to get out there and raise some funds
籌款了嗎
for St. Abigail's Hospital?
我希望是準備好了
I hope the answer's yes because those nuns
那些修女盯我可盯得很緊
are breathing down my neck.
Harris 見我笑 錢包開
Harris, this smile opens wallets.
看著
Watch this.
好 都注意好躲開
Okay, get ready to duck.
在后面的也不安全哦
And don't think you're safe back there either.
哇
Whoo!
那是我老公
- That's my husband. -
誰要在這么漂亮的一桿后面打可慘了啊
Hate to be the guy who has to follow that.
不過話說 是誰要和我一起打
Who am I partnered with anyway?
一個叫Chaz Garrity的
Oh, just a little someone by the name of Chaz Garrity.
爵士音樂家
The jazz musician.
他在肯尼迪中心表演過
He played the Kennedy Center.
五點檔新聞的主題曲就是他寫的
He wrote the theme for our 5:00 News, Mike.
- 噢 我喜歡那段  - 是啊
- Oh, I love that. - Yeah.
高爾夫也打得很好
Hell of a golfer too.
這點尤其厲害
Which is amazing,
考慮到他的個人因素
considering his personal challenges.
他在哪兒
There he is.
- 那人  - 沒錯
- That guy? - Yeah.
我在籌款 Mike 各個社會名流都來幫忙了
I'm raising funds here, Mike. Every celebrity helps.
所以我們回到了1961年
So it's 1961,
爵士音樂家又成了社會名流了嗎
and jazz musicians are celebrities again?
爵士是唯一純粹的美國藝術
Hey, jazz is the only pure American art form.
過去打個招呼把
Now go over there and say hello.
行
Yeah.
嗨 Chaz
Hey, Chaz.
你怎么樣 我們今天一起打球
How you doing? I guess we're partners today.
挺出人意料的 是吧
This is kind of surprising, isn't it?
出人意料 怎么 因為我是盲人嗎
"Surprising"? Why, 'cause I'm blind?
不 因為我們之前遇見過
Well, no, no. But because we met earlier.
而且 我有帕金森
And-- and, you know, I have Parkinson's.
我能理解克服個人
So I know something about overcoming personal--
障礙
Obstacles?
- 你想說這個嗎  - 障礙 是的
- Is that what you were gonna say? - Obstacles, yeah.
聽著 我可不想被拖進
Listen, I don't want to get dragged down
你那悲慘 消極的世界
into your sad, negative world, dude.
我是來玩的
I'm just here to play a game.
悲慘
- - "Sad"?
得了吧
Come on.
哇
Whoo!
哇哦
Oh, wow.
聽上去不錯
That sounded good.
打了多遠 我看不見
Hey, how far did that go? I couldn't see it.
好球
Nice shot.
哇
Yes! Oh, wow!
聽吶
Listen to that!
聽上去會是小鳥球啊
Sounds like a birdie.
小鳥球 指高爾夫中低于標準桿一桿的成績
情侶按摩時間
Couples massage time.
準備好在另一個男人摸我的時候跟我眉來眼去了嗎
You ready to make eye contact while another guy touches me?
親愛的 我得把這場打完
Oh, honey. I-I gotta finish this game.
這Chaz在跟我較勁兒
This Chaz guy called me out.
"跟你較勁兒" 你還是16歲么
"Called you out"? What, are you 16?
你要在寡婦彎道跟他一較高下
You gonna drag race him down widow's curve?
Widow's Curve 極度危險的彎道
當然不 親愛的 他是盲人 不能開車
Of course not, honey. He's blind. He can't drive.
我還以為這周末
I thought this weekend
你只打幾個球
you were just gonna hit a few balls
剩下的時間都是屬于我倆的
and the rest of the time was gonna be about us.
謝謝你能理解
Thanks for understanding.
很難做到嗎 當然
Is it hard? Yeah, sure.
但我練成了這雙手
But I've trained my hands to have sight
能見雙眼所不見
where my eyes don't.
順便一提 你的微笑很美
Beautiful smile, by the way.
把電話給這個人
Give this guy your number.
- Chaz  - 干嘛
- Chaz. - Yeah?
我能給你提個醒嗎
Can I give you a little tip
一個勵志人物給另一個提的醒
from one inspirational guy to another?
大家都知道你是盲人
Everybody knows you're blind.
你說什么
Excuse me?
我覺得你有些在利用這一點
You're just-- you're milking it a little.
- 我在  - 只是一點
- I'm-- - Just a little.
我在利用這點
I'm milking it?
我可沒說
Okay, I wasn't the one who said,
"我有帕金森 這是種障礙"
"I have Parkinson's. It's an obstacle."
那今天你在大廳里呢
Oh, how about you in the lobby today?
我是盲人 我是盲人
"I'm blind. I'm blind.
我要風景好的房間 我是盲人
Give me a room with a view! I'm blind!"
我是來這兒玩的
Oh, wow, man, I came here to have fun,
可是現在我眼前一片憤怒的血紅
and now I'm just seeing red.
或者說 我能想象出的紅色
Or at least my idea of what red is.
- 愛你 Chaz  - 加油啊 Chaz
- Love you, Chaz! - Way to go, Chaz!
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦 不用的 Mike
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Take it easy, Mike.
有球童的
We got a caddy for that.
讓他回去吧
Send him home.
我自己來
I'm carrying this burden on my own.
你是個英雄 Mike
You're my hero, Mike.
我還要拿這個
And I'm gonna take his too.
嗨 Larry
Hey, there, Larry.
我和你的同事Maurice
I believe I spoke to your associate Maurice
電話聯系過了
on the phone.
我們有預訂 登記在Ian Henry名下
We have a reservation under Ian Henry.
抱歉 孩子們
Sorry, kids.
你們要想約炮 去別地兒去
If you want to hook up, do it somewhere else.
等等 你以為我們是
Wait, you think that we're a--
惡 惡 惡 惡 真惡心
Ew, ew, ew, ew! Disgusting!
哥們兒 這是我妹妹
Come on, man. This is my sister.
- 沒錯  - 恩哼
- Yeah. - Uh-huh.
- 這招早聽過了  - 我來搞定
- Heard that before. - I got this.
Lar 關于這個亂倫的事情
Look, Lar, I think we got off on the wrong foot
我們起了個壞頭
with the whole incest thing.
或許我的朋友 Jackson總統
Maybe my friend, President Jackson,
Andrew Jackson 美國第七位總統 其肖像被印在20美元的鈔票上
能幫我們解決這個問題
can help ease out the situation.
你有見過他的雙胞胎弟弟
And have you met his twin brother,
第二任期的總統Jackson嗎
second term President Jackson?
抱歉 幫不了你們
Sorry, can't help you guys.
我懂了
I see what's going on here.
我一回家 你就等著上Yelp吧
The second I get home, you're getting Yelped!
Yelp 美國最大的點評網站
沒錯 就是你
Okay? Yeah. Yeah, you.
我要全部寫上去
I'm mentioning everything!
包括這個大廳 這個男的
I'm mentioning this lobby, I'm mentioning this guy,
還有這兩只熊
and the bears!
你現在落后三竿感覺怎么樣
How does it feel to be three strokes
還是落后給法律承認的盲人
behind a man who's legally blind?
法律承認
"Legally blind"?
等一下 你是說 法律承認的盲人么
Wait a minute, did you say "Legally blind"?
這話什么意思 你能看到大概的形狀嗎
What does that mean? Can you see shapes?
我不知道 你看得到形狀嗎
I don't know. Can you see shapes?
沒人看到嗎
Nobody saw that?
竟然沒人看到 真不敢相信
Nobody saw that? Unbelievable.
沒人看到
Nobody saw that.
天
Unbelievable.
- 加油 chaz  - 你可以的
- Come on, Chaz. - You can make it.
好的
Okay.
加油 Chaz
Come on, Chaz.
干嘛啊 小破孩
Come on, kid.
媽媽爸爸們 幫幫忙管好你家孩子 行不
Mom, dad, help us out here, will you please?
真是豈有此理
For crying out loud.
該我了
My turn.
球進洞啦
It's in the hole!
好的 接下來把桿B插進襯套Q里
Okay, so just put pole "B" Into grommet "Q."
這樣應該差不多了
And that should be good.
沒有旅館同意讓我們住 所以我們買了個帳篷花了200塊
No hotel would take us, so we bought a tent for $200.
我覺得賣我們帳篷的家伙敲了我們的竹杠
I think the guy who sold it to us ripped us off.
是啊 他肯定是把我們兩個當情侶了
Yeah, and he definitely thought we were a couple.
好像我們散發出了搞在一塊兒的感覺似的
What, are we giving off some sort of chemistry vibe?
- 喔 惡 惡心 - 你還能再惡點
- Oh, ew, gross. - You could do worse.
這樣也挺不錯的
This isn't so bad.
我們大賺一筆
We're making a tasty profit,
還能在這兒享受下大自然
and we're out here enjoying nature.
簡直就是雙贏
It's a win-win.
不要
No!
你沒放點東西進去壓著帳篷嗎
You didn't put anything in there to weigh it down?
沒 只放了我的錢包進去 媽的 噢
No, just my wallet. Damn it! Oh!
算了別說了 我們趕緊走吧
You know what, let's just get out of here.
有沒有搞錯
Seriously?
哦 拜托
Oh, come on!
噢 這讓我想起來以前
Oh, this reminds me when I used to
小的時候玩過家家
throw tea parties as a kid.
我把洋娃娃扮作客人
My dolls would be the guests,
然后我讓Mike做服務員
and I'd make Mike be the waiter.
酷 是的 真不錯
Cool. Yeah. Totally.
你到底有沒有在聽 Graham
Are you even listening, Graham?
當然了 恩
Totally. Yeah.
原來跟我8歲的小外甥約會
Turns out going on a date with my eight-year-old nephew
跟其他男人約會沒什么兩樣
is just like going on a date with any other guy.
抱歉我來晚了 但是有所收獲哦
I'm sorry I'm late, but it wasn't all for naught.
我贏了這個
I got this.
- 這么說來你贏了  - 沒有
- So you won. - Oh, God, no.
這是參與獎
That's a participation trophy.
我是第二十三名
No, I came in 23rd.
但是Chaz第二十五
But Chaz came in 25th.
Mike 我真不敢相信你毀了我們的周末
Mike, I can't believe you ruined our weekend
就為了爭這么一點兒
all over some grudge match
還是跟一個人挺好的盲人
with a perfectly nice blind person.
我就說怎么聽見一個成人的聲音
I thought I heard the voice of an adult
從小孩兒身高的位置傳出來
coming from the height range of a child.
哇
Whoa.
你故意把那袋子推翻
You deliberately knocked over that bag,
害我打偏那桿 你個作弊小人
so I'd miss that putt, you cheater.
嗨 我老公才不會作弊
Hey, my husband is not a cheater.
是 還是不是 這些都不重要
"Is," "Isn't..." It's not important.
真正重要的是我們要吃頓浪漫晚餐
What is important is that we have that romantic dinner
我們說好的 我現在就開始想客房服務了
we talked about-- I'm thinking room service.
躲開晚宴 是吧
Skipping the banquet, huh?
你自己都覺得自己在宴會上丟人吧
Figured you'd be too ashamed to show your voice.
哇哦 這人我真是看走眼了
Wow, was I wrong about that guy.
真是個混蛋 竟然說你作弊
What a jerk. And to call you a cheater?
真是個瘋子 對吧
Crazy, huh?
那啥 至少這事兒到此為止了
Well, at least that story's over with.
我想吃意大利菜 你呢
I'm feeling Italian. How about you?
不要 去他的浪漫
No, screw romance.
我們就是要參加那個晚宴
We are going to that banquet.
去斐濟玩怎么樣 我請客
How about Fiji? My treat.
寶貝兒 我們可以不用來的
Honey, we don't have to do this.
我們可以溜走 沿著海邊散散步吹吹風
We can knock off, we can go take a long walk by the ocean.
Mike 這兒是大西洋城
Mike, it's the Atlantic.
從我們家窗戶就能看見那爛海
We can see that garbage ocean from our apartment.
我們來這兒是要贏回一局的
We're here to settle a score.
- 大度點  - 晚上好
- Be cool. - Good evening.
我謹代表新聞四臺
On behalf of Channel Four News, thank you
感謝各位來支持圣阿比蓋爾醫院
for coming out to support the research wing
研究翼樓的建設
of St. Abigail's Hospital.
今天我們募集到超過1500元
And today we raised over $1,500--
什么 沒錯吧
What? Was that it?
好吧
All right.
我剛得知我們要改為
Well, I've been told we're switching
現售吧臺了
to a cash bar.
cash bar 來賓需自己花錢買酒open bar 酒由主辦方出資提供
請各位享用晚餐吧
Enjoy your meals.
可以的話 我想要說幾句話
I'd like to say a few words if I may.
別擔心 我不會把你的晚餐騙走的
Don't worry, I won't cheat you out of your dinners.
因為眾所周知
Because as we all know,
作弊 -- 不論是在高爾夫球
cheating-- whether it be at golf
還是生活的其他方面 -- 都是可恥的
or any of life's endeavors-- is truly despicable.
不論如何 來到這里都是一種榮幸
Anyways, it's an honor to be here.
這是個非常偉大的事業 請盡情享用晚餐
This is a great, great cause. And enjoy your meals.
快說點什么呀
Say something.
能來到這里實在是榮幸之極
I too am honored to be here.
給圣Abigail醫院捐款
Giving to St. Abigail's is
就如同在給未來做投資
like an investment in the future.
大家都知道 我們的孩子才是未來
And we all know that our children are the future.
比如這個男孩兒
Like this boy here.
懂得保持低調
The kind of kid who knows to keep his head down
也不多說話
and not say too much and...
知道分寸
know his place.
再次重申 這是個非常 非常 非常
So once again, it's a great, great, great,
非常 非常 非常 偉大的事業
great, great, great, great cause.
我們別把它搞砸了
And let's not do anything to screw it up.
請享用晚餐吧
Enjoy the meal.
- 就這么點  - 是的 就這樣吧
- That's it? - Yeah, let's go.
嗨 我是Annie Henry  Mike的妻子
Hi. Annie Henry, Mike's wife.
我也很榮幸
Also honored.
我覺得這位廣告曲作家
I think that the jingle writer
關于作弊說的話非常對
made a good point about cheating.
還有一點是 如果我們不支持
Another point-- if we don't support
圣Abigail醫院 難道我們就都是輸家嗎
St. Abigail's, aren't we all losers?
也許我們中有些人 是輸不起
Maybe some of us, sore losers.
還有比這種輸不起的人
And is there anything worse
更糟的嗎
than a sore loser?
除了這個研究試圖
Other than the diseases that this research
要治愈的疾病之外
is trying to cure?
這是個 好 很好 非常好 真是
This is a great, great, super great, really,
堪稱最好的事業了
just the best cause.
請享用各位的晚餐
Enjoy your meal.
我能不能再來一杯果汁
Can I get some more juice?
你這已經是第五杯了
That was your fifth glass.
你喝得夠多了
Maybe you've had enough.
我回家也能喝的
I could get this at home.
樓上有蘋果汁的
We have apple juice upstairs.
無聲拍賣正式結束
And the silent auction is now officially closed.
主辦方在桌子上放置拍賣單，競拍者只需在物品下填寫出價即可
我很驕傲的宣布 我們籌集到了
I'm proud to announce that we have raised...
250美元
$250?
真是夠了
All right. That's it.
把巧克力噴泉關掉
Turn off the chocolate fountain.
要是不加番茄醬
If you're not gonna use the ketchup,
那就別把瓶子打開
don't open the bottles just for the hell of it.
厲害啊 Henry
Real nice, Henry.
讓你的老婆幫你打嘴仗
Getting your wife to fight your battles for you?
你得承認她很厲害
Well, you have to admit she's good at it.
你對一個法律承認的盲人作弊了
Hey, hey, you cheated against a legally blind man.
法律承認
Legally blind?
Mike 他能看見形狀
Mike, this guy can see shapes.
我一直在說這事兒
That's what I've been saying.
真是可笑 閃開
Okay, this is ridiculous. Out of the way.
你怎么知道Mike站那兒的
Hey, how did you know where Mike was?
除非
Unless...
接著
Think fast!
這什么也證明不了
Well, that didn't prove anything.
我們這就走
We'll show ourselves out.
你拿龍蝦砸了一個盲人 一下子
You hit one blind dude with a lobster, and then, oh, suddenly,
- 你就成了壞人了  - 我明白
- you're the bad guy. - I know.
我們才是受害者
We're the victims here.
哦 看
Oh, look at this.
看吶 看吶
Lookee, lookee.
海景套房
Ocean view suite.
門大開著
Wide open.
他們說都訂滿了
They said it was all full.
這本來是屬于我們的海景
That was supposed to be our view.
進去看看也無傷大雅吧
Well, it wouldn't hurt to take a little peek.
沒錯 大海
Yep, that's an ocean.
過來 試試從這邊看怎么樣
Come and see what it looks like from over here.
但那邊要遠一些啊
But that's further away.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I see what you're doing.
你沒開玩笑吧 干嘛鎖上
Ugh, are you serious? Why would you lock this?
不讓別人像我們這樣進去啊
So that people like us can't get in.
說得好
Solid point.
真是史上最爛的一夜
Worst night ever.
這就是我們的下場
This is what we get.
媽媽和爸爸那么信任我們
Mom and dad put a roof over our head,
- 我們卻在背后捅他們刀子  - 過了這么一天
- and we stab them in the back.  - After the day we've had,
我以后一定會尊重爸媽
I am never disrespecting mom and dad again.
好吧 我才不要像一只鴿子一樣
All right, well, I'm not sleeping
睡在外面
out here like a pigeon.
我要把鎖撬開
I am gonna jimmy open that lock
用這個腰帶
with this belt--
不
No!
那要八十美元呢 這樣我們賺的錢就都沒了
Oh, that was $80. Now we're not making any money.
我才不要把我的那份也花在你的破腰帶上
I'm not paying for your cheesy belt!
這是阿瑪尼休閑 你真是沒有時尚感
It was Armani Exchange! You have no sense of fashion.
- 你在逗我嗎  - 一點都沒有
- Are you serious? - Just zero.
親愛的
Honey?
這有對無家可歸的小兩口
There's a homeless couple
在防火梯上吵架呢
having a lovers' quarrel on the fire escape.
- 不 我們住這兒  - 我們也不是小兩口
- No, we live here. - And we're not a couple!
怎么回事
What's going on?
我們說實話吧
Let's just tell them the truth.
好
You're right.
我們的父母這周末把公寓租了出去
Our parents rented out the apartment for the weekend
我們沒地方去了
and left us with nowhere to go.
噢 可憐的孩子
Oh, you poor things.
這太過分了
That's awful.
進來吧 我給你們拿攤子
Come in. We'll get you some blankets.
親愛的 幫幫我
Honey, help me.
說好的不給爸媽背后捅刀呢
What ever happened to not betraying mom and dad?
- 我好冷  - 好吧
- I was cold. - Yeah. Ooh.
身材保持的真好
Stay in form.
謝謝你
Thank you very much.
我發誓我讓門開著
I could have sworn I left it open,
好讓我能再找到的
so I could find it again.
因為我是盲人嘛
You know, 'cause I'm blind.
哎
Here we go.
一下也別動
Keep perfectly still.
你知道你在和誰說話對吧
You know who you're talking to, right?
你說的沒錯 我能看見形狀
You were right. I can see shapes.
哇哦
Skiddily wow.
- 噢  - 就是這個人栽贓我
- Oh.  - That's the guy who blamed me
弄翻了高爾夫球袋
for knocking over the golf bag!
我站起來說了你那么多好話
And after all the nice things I said about you in my speech...
混蛋
Son of a--
你陷害了一個十歲小孩兒
So you framed a ten-year-old kid.
毫不為此驕傲
Not my proudest moment.
今天到底是怎么了
What happened today?
一般來說 你只是為了玩得開心
Usually, you're just happy to have fun out there.
你打高爾夫不會這么好勝的
It's not like you to be so competitive about golf.
不是高爾夫的問題
Oh, it wasn't about the golf.
我只是想要塑造勵志形象而已
I just want to be the inspirational guy.
我想這已經在我的身份里
I mean, I guess it's become
占據了比我意識到的還要多的位置
a bigger part of my identity than I realized.
如果這么說能讓你好受點
If it makes you feel any better,
對于真正了解你的人來說
to the people who really know you,
你并不是很勵志啊
you're not all that inspiring.
- 完全沒讓我好受點  - 我只是說
- Doesn't help.  - I'm just saying.
對孩子們來說 你是個親切的爸爸
To the kids, you're an embarrassing dad.
對我來說 你是靈魂伴侶兼搶被子的
To me, you're a soul mate/blanket hog.
面對現實吧 對那個純潔的十歲小孩
And let's face it, to that innocent ten-year-old boy,
你不過是一個大騙子
you are nothing but a big, fat cheater.
"純潔" 他看著就賊眉鼠眼的
"Innocent"? He had shifty eyes.
往好的方面想
On the bright side,
我想我們不會再被邀請
I don't think we'll be invited
去任何周末高爾夫活動了
to any more golf weekends.
所以這都是你的秘密計劃的一部分
So this was all part of your secret plan?
我只是想待在
I'm just glad to be somewhere
我們不會被人說三道四的地方
where we won't be judged.
哼哼
Well, well, well.
如果來的不是史上最差父母
If it isn't the worst parents ever.
你倆該進監獄
You two should be in prison.
你們回來早了啊
You're home early.
這些人是誰 這些小孩是誰
Who are these people? Who are these children?
- 啊  - 電影時間
- Ah!  - Movie time.
看什么 <火爆群龍> 還是 <野鴨變鳳凰>
What's it gonna be, Slap Shot or Mighty Ducks?
真的嗎 兩部冰球電影 就只能選這些
Seriously, two hockey movies? Those are my choices?
被禁足了就是這樣
That's what happens when you're grounded.
- 但是 媽  - 再廢話
- But, mom...  - Keep it up,
就看兩部
and you watch both.
你們的處境很危險哦
You're on thin ice. Huh?
有時候 你得習慣扮演某個角色
Sometimes, you get used to playing certain roles.
破冰者 嘿 伙計
Icebreaker, hey, buddy.
或許是雄心壯志的
Maybe you're the ambitious one
聰明的 或是 勵志的
or the smart one or the inspiring one.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
但是你不能讓
- - But you can't let
這些角色擺布你  - 你好
- those roles define you.  - Hello?
- 嘿 Leigh姑姑  - 是你啊
- Hey, Aunt Leigh.  - Oh. It's you.
嗨
Hey.
要來看電影嗎
Want to come watch a movie?
我馬上就去
I'll be right up.
他第二天打電話來了
He called the next day.
哦
Oh!
如果你太在意他人的看法
Because if you're too caught up in how other people see you,
你可能會忘了要停下來欣賞風景
you might forget to stop and enjoy the view.
我覺得這比斐濟島更好
You know, I think this is better than Fiji.
你是我的月亮 我是海龜
Well, you are my moon, and I am the sea turtle
爬過波利尼西亞的熱沙灘
paddling across the hot Polynesian sands--
- 忘了吧  - Uno
- Oh, forget it.  - Uno!
Uno 一種牌類游戲,當玩家手上只余下一張牌時，必須喊出"uno"
該死
Darn it.
他們不打算走嗎
Are they ever gonna leave?
怎么 他們付了推遲退房的錢
What? They paid for late checkout.
抱歉 我可不想上Yelp
Sorry, I don't want to get Yelped.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組